Guide to the Roy Eaton papers, 1860-2016 and undated. RL.11520
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1955-2014 and undated; 7
  - Video Tapes, 1976-2007 and undated; 6
    - Apollo Games (Benton & Bowles)--Mystery Planet FP; Space Cavern FP, 1982 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-004)
    - AT&T Corporate (N.W. Ayer)--Funding Credit MacNeil Lehrer Newshour :15, 1985 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-005)
    - BAMS Alex "On the Road", undated (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-006)
    - Beech-Nut Nutrition (Sherwood & Schneider), 1982 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-007)
      Stages "Home Movies" :60; Table Time "Disappear" :30
    - Black & Decker "Liberty" new arrangement :30, undated (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-008)
    - Burger King, 1985 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-009)
      Promo Doubles/The Three Quarters :30
    - Burger King, 1985 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-010)
      Croissandwich/Who Beat :30
    - Cella (Jos. Garneau/Benton & Bowles), 1985 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-011)
      Deck the Halls/FP
    - CDC (Centers for Disease Control and Prevention) AIDS PSA, 1988 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-012)
      Body Builder; Mother :30
    - CDC (Centers for Disease Control and Prevention) AIDS PSA--Body Builder, 1988 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-013)
    - Chase Credit Card "Flexible", 1991 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-014)
    - Chrysler (Lockhart & Pettus), 1988 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-015)
      LeBaron convertible "Fashion"; Dodge Daytona "Classical/Jazz" :30 and :60
    - Chrysler 1989 spots (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-016)
      Killer Joe; Eagle "I Wish I Knew That"
    - Chrysler (Lockhart & Pettus), 1991 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-017)
      Imperial "Barber Shop", "Dynasty", "Banker"
    - Chrysler (Lockhart & Pettus), 1993 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-018)
      New Yorker "Steppin Out" :30
    - Chrysler "Down Home" :60 and :30, 1993 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-019)
    - Chrysler (Lockhart & Pettus), 1991 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-020)
      Jeep Cherokee "Coltrane" :30
    - Coca-Cola (Burrell Advertising), 1990 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-021)
      Bill Cosby/Zydeco/Mono :30
    - Coca-Cola "Thomas Edison" :30, 1995 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-022)
    - Coca-Cola (Creative Artists Agency) "Urban" directed by John Singleton, 1994 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-023)
    - Crystal Starr and Friends; Moon Dreamer episode, undated (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-024)
    - Dark and Lovely, 1989 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-025)
    - Diet Coke/Caffeine Free "The Best Things in Life Are Free", undated (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-026)
    - Fidelity Bank (Lewis Gillman & Kynett), 1986 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-027)
      Image-Uncommon Value "Clockmaker" :30; "Teacher" :30
    - Fidelity Bank (Lewis Gillman & Kynett), 1986 (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-028)
      Image "Architect" :30
    - Fidelity Bank spots, undated (Box AV30, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-029)
      Rowers A :30; Rowers B :30; Clockmaker :30; Teacher :30
    - First FRM (Post Expressions), undated (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-030)
    - Hardee's (Benton & Bowles) "Celebrate" I and 2, 1982 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-031)
    - Hardee's (Benton & Bowles) "Mouthful", undated (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-032)
    - Infinity Factory II (Project One) show 213 30:00, 1976 (?) (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-033)
    - Infinity Factory II (Project One) show 224 30:00, 1976 (?) (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-034)
    - Jeep Grand Cherokee (Lockhart & Pettus), 1993 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-035)
      Down Home ver. 1 (Quincy), ver. 2 (Toots) polished rough cut :60
    - Jeep Grand Cherokee (Lockhart & Pettus), 1993 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-036)
    - Kodak (J. Walter Thompson) spots, undated (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-037)
      Duck Decoy :30; Sports Sculpture :30
    - Kodak (J. Walter Thompson) spots, undated (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-038)
      Beethoven :10; Whitman :10; Da Vinci :10
    - Marine Midland, 1985 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-039)
      Countdown; Close Enough; Low Interest
    - Milton Bradley--Battleball :30, 1989 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-040)
    - Milton Bradley--Lite Brite :30, :10, undated (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-041)
    - Milton Bradley--Lite Brite :30, 1988 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-042)
    - Nabisco corporate "Marwood" :60, undated (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-043)
    - Newsweek (Leber Katz & Partners) "Commitment" ver. A, 1983 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-044)
    - Newsweek (Leber Katz & Partners) "Commitment", 1983 (Box AV31, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-045)
    - Newsweek (Leber Katz & Partners) "Commitment II", 1984 (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-046)
    - Pantene (Richardson Vicks/Leber Katz & Partners)--"Don't Hate Me"; Dancer :30, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-047)
    - Pantene (Richardson Vicks/Leber Katz & Partners)--"Reclining Woman" ver. A, 1984 (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-048)
    - Pantene (Richardson Vicks/Leber Katz & Partners)--"Reclining Woman" ver. A, 1984 (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-049)
    - Pennsylvania Lottery (Lewis Gilman & Kynett)--Beautiful Dreamer 1 and 2 :30, 1988 (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-050)
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-051)
      Black & Decker; Classic Beer
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-052)
      Data General; Newsweek; Pantene
    - Roy Eaton Music--Rich Meitin producer reel, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-053)
      Eastern; Noxzema; Diet Coke; New York State; Cover Girl Nails; Luna Mystique; Impulse; Noxz
    - Roy Eaton Music--Rich Meitin sound design and scoring reel 12 tracks, 1991 (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-054)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Schmidt's "Clear"; Black & Decker "Liberty" (Lewis Gilman & Kynett), undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-055)
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-056)
      Newsweek; Pantene "Dancer"; Drunk Driving "Beat It"; Woman's Day "Deaf Child"
    - Roy Eaton Music--Music and sound design reel 14 tracks, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-057)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Music and sound design reel 14 tracks, undated (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-058)
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation master, 1989 (Box AV32, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-059)
      AIDS PSA: AT&T; Dodge Daytona; Pantene; Burger King; Fidelity Bank; Moon Dreamers; Newsweek
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-060)
      Burger King; AT&T; Fidelity Bank; Woman's Day; Wendy's; Marine Midland; Sports Channel; Newsweek; Black & Decker
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation, 1982 (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-061)
      Fiat; Texaco; Texas Commerce Bank; Hardee's; Romper Room; Tortoise & Hare; Crest; Crum & Forster; Planters Nuts; Ivory Shampoo
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation master, 1985 (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-062)
      Burger King; Atlantic Bell; Pantene; Sports Channel; Wendy's; Drunk Driving; Newsweek; Black & Decker
    - Runner-Up Sportswear, 1982 (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-063)
    - Sports Channel; Wendy's, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-064)
    - Texaco (Benton & Bowles) "Egg" :60, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-065)
    - Texaco (Benton & Bowles) "Pavarotti II" :60, 1982 (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-066)
    - Texaco (Benton & Bowles) "Star Opener" :30; "Egg" :60, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-067)
    - Texaco (Benton & Bowles) "Star Opener" :30; "Egg" :60; Apollo, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-068)
    - Texas Commerce Bank (Benton & Bowles)--"Bankers" 6 versions; "Real Estate" :30, 1985 (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-069)
    - United Way spots, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-070)
      American Way; Citizens Review; Family Crisis
    - U.S. Postal Service (Young & Rubicam)--Olympics promotion :30, undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-071)
    - Wisk Powder (BBDO)--"Angel"; "Wedding", 1986 (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-072)
    - Woman's Day (Leber Katz Partners)--"Deaf Child"; "Infertility", undated (Box AV33, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-073)
    - Chrysler spots, 1988 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-001)
      Class Act; Fashion; Classical/Jazz
    - Buck and the Preacher, undated (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-002)
    - Chrysler "Parking Lot", 1992 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-003)
    - Coca-Cola--Coke Classic "Skyline" :30, 1997 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-004)
    - Coca-Cola--Coke Classic "Skyline" :30, 1997 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-005)
    - Edison, undated (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-006)
    - Lumina Video Magazine, 1988 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-007)
      Buckwheat Zydeco; Senate Bill for Artist Rights; Jahn; Susan Marshall; David T. Hanson; One-ring Circus; Georgia O'Keefe
    - Pantene--Don't Hate Me :30, 1986 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-008)
    - Pianists for Peace, 2007 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-009)
    - The Power of Faith/The Planet Is Alive (Robert Evans) 42:00, 1987 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-010)
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation 12 tracks 5:00, undated (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-011)
    - Roy Eaton Music compilation 18 tracks, undated (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-012)
    - Sports Channel, 1985 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-013)
      Islander Open; Nets Open; New Music
    - Southwest Airlines (GSD&M)--"Backyard" :30, 2005 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-014)
    - Target (Martin/Williams), 1997 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-015)
      Rhythm of Summer/Stomp :30; July Go/Stomp :30
    - Texaco--Harvey's Place "Bride and Groom" :20, 1986 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-016)
    - Think (Aretha Franklin) 4:00, undated (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-017)
    - Yava Pai Stories short version (Women Make Movies) 58:38, 1992 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-018)
    - Yava Pai Stories (Women Make Movies: Kathy Fredricks), 1992 (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-VHS-019)
    - Linda Hopkins guest appearances on television, undated (Box AV34, Video-cassette RL11520-Bcam-001)
  - Other Audiovisual Formats, 1957-2014 and undated; 7
    - Roy Eaton--Complete Preludes of Chopin, Gershwin, Still; Summit DCD-318, 2002 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-001)
    - Roy Eaton--DVD draft, 2014 (Box AV34, Video-disc RL11520-OP-002)
    - Roy Eaton--I Play for Peace; Rhahm Music, 2011 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-003)
    - Roy Eaton--Joplin Piano Rags; Sony Legacy Essential Classics SBK 89886, 2002 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-004)
    - Roy Eaton--Keyboard Classics for Children; Summit DCD-471, 2007 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-005)
    - Roy Eaton--The Meditative Chopin; Rhahm Music RHM001, 2008 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-006)
    - Various Artists--A Very Green Christmas (Artists for Earth); Seventh Wave SWP-7091-2, 1997 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-007)
      Roy Eaton featured on track 15
    - Fox News--Ailes Apprentice Program Celebrates Black History Month, 2014 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-008)
      Roy Eaton interviewed
    - You See What You Hear 8:00, 2014 (Box AV34, Audio-cd RL11520-OP-009)
    - Crest "Water" :90, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-001)
    - Dana Perfume (Benton & Bowles) "Tabu" :30, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-002)
    - Empathy "Dead End Day" (Benton & Bowles), undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-003)
    - Fiat (Benton & Bowles) "House on Wheels" :30, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-004)
    - Hardee's (Benton & Bowles) "Dreamer" :30, 1979 (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-005)
    - Human rights compilation, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-006)
      Dead End Day; Rejected Child; Home; Puerto Rican Boy
    - Kent "What a Good Time"; "Race Track" :30, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-007)
    - Lakeside Toys (Shaller Rubin) "Super Flexees" :60, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-008)
    - Pepto Bismol (Benton & Bowles) "Lonely Boy" :60, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-009)
    - Presbyterian print works (animation), undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-010)
    - Texaco (Benton & Bowles) "Glass Blower" :60, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-011)
    - Texaco (Benton & Bowles) "Tough Hole Hope" :60, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-012)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-013)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-014)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton--16mm master, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-015)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton--16mm master, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-016)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton--16mm color comp print, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-017)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton--Work print, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-018)
    - You See What You Hear (Benton & Bowles) directed and written by Roy Eaton; Beefaroni :60, undated (Box AV35, Film-reel RL11520-F16-019)
    - 6x16 B Wind Parts, undated (Box AV25, Film-reel RL11520-F35-001)
    - Up the Avenue--Ed Corley, Director; Roy Eaton music, undated (Box AV25, Film-reel RL11520-F35-002)
    - A Girl--Gene Schinto, Roy Eaton; vocal Don Casanave. 10" 78 rpm, undated (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-001)
    - Brighter Day--Words and music by Roy Eaton. 10", undated (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-002)
    - Jell-O radio 6 sec. Patter Flavor, sides 3 and 4. 20 tracks. Mutual Recording 104877. 12", 33 1/3 rpm., undated (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-003)
    - Johnson & Johnson Baby Powder and Oil (Young & Rubicam). WCR Recording 110908. 10" 78 rpm, 1958 (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-004)
    - Kent Cigarettes (Young & Rubicam). AV1851. 12" 33 1/3 rpm. 8 tracks, 1957 (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-005)
    - Kent Cigarettes (Young & Rubicam). Dealer spots AV1851. 12" 33 1/3 rpm. 8 tracks, 1957 (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-006)
    - Kent Cigarettes (Young & Rubicam). Dealer spots AV1851. 12" 33 1/3 rpm. 8 tracks, 1957 (Box AV25, Audio-phonodisc RL11520-PD-007)
    - Roy Eaton Music demo/show reel duplicates (1/4 audiotape) (Box AV36)
    - Miscellaneous duplicate audio reels and cassettes (Box AV37)